

## CONTACT

+351 926 348 627

a.marta.gato@hotmail.com

martasportfolio.netlify.app

Lisboa

linkedin.com/in/marta-santos-lx/

## EDUCATION

# Bachelor in Computer Sciences

2017 – **2020**: Licenciatura em Engenharia Informática at **Faculdade de Ciências da Universidade de Lisboa**, with a grade of 17 (out of 20). – Academic Merit Diploma.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

Angular
Vue.js
Javascript
HTML
CSS
Jest
Java
Git
Jira

## MARTA **SANTOS**

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### ABOUT ME

With 3 years of experience in the field, I am confident in delivering efficient and creative technical solutions. My journey has equipped me with a fluent understanding of modern frontend frameworks and agile methodologies. I am eager to mature my skills and participate in high-quality product development in a collaborative team environment.

#### EXPERIENCE

## **Frontend Developer**

**Polarising** 

Sep 2022 - Present

- FrontEnd development in Angular (v15) recreating legacy code into Angular components.
- FrontEnd development in Vue.js (2) migrating legacy code from .net to Vue.js components.

## Salesforce Developer

CGI

Apr 2021 - Jul 2022

- FrontEnd development building SalesForce apps in LWC (Component-based Javascript library) - replicating look and functionality from a legacy project in .net into LWC.
- Also did some BackEnd work in this project Apex (SF Java equivalent).

## **Private Tutor**

Explica, Marta!

Sep 2020 - Apr 2021

• Math and Science tutoring (5th to 12th grade).

## LANGUAGE

Portuguese English Spanish French

## EXTRACURRICULAR

- WWOOF (Organic farming volunteering)
- Science Illustration (Nature Illustration Yearly Course, Museu Nacional de História Natural e da Ciência, Lisbon)